Register to The Benny Goodman Papers
Yale University Music Library
- Band and Combo Arrangements
  - SOMEBODY STOLE MY GAL Henderson, Fletcher, 1940 (Box 24F, Folder 50)
    BG No.: B58
    Score: original and photocopy w/ vocal insert (see notes)
    Vocal insert (included with photocopy of score) replaces 2 measures before rehearsal B to letter D in original score.
  - SOMEBODY'S WRONG (Box 25, Folder 01)
    BG No.: A224/236/C1O8
  - SOMEBODY'S WRONG, 1946 (Box 25, Folder 02)
    BG No.: C301/A60
    Parts: cl/saxAATT/tpt2-3/tbn1-2/PGB
    Written for Roy McKinley.
  - SOMEDAY SWEETHEART Henderson, Fletcher, 1936 (Box 25, Folder 03)
    BG No.: C229/84/15/44
    Parts: cl/saxAATT/tpt1-3/tbn1-3(2)/G(2)BD
  - SOMEDAY SWEETHEART Henderson, Fletcher, 1936 (Box 25, Folder 03A)
    BG No.: 22
    Parts are a recopy.
  - SOMEONE'S ROCKIN' MY DREAM BOAT Powell, Mel, 1941 (Box 25, Folder 04)
    BG No.: B219
  - SOMETHING Lieb, Dick, c.1970 (Box 25, Folder 05)
    BG No.: G126/S7
  - SOMETHING NEW Sauter, Eddie, 1941 (Box 25, Folder 06)
    BG No.: B182/30
    Tpt4 and tbn3 are not indicated in score. Complete.
  - SOMETIMES Sauter, Eddie, 1941 (Box 25, Folder 07)
    BG No.: B211
  - SOMETIMES I'M HAPPY Henderson, Fletcher, 1935 (Box 25A, Folder 08)
    BG No.: C346/SB/7/23/17
    Parts: cl/saxATTB(-A1)/tPt3-4/tbn1-2/PGBD
    1948 recopy. C1 part is a photocopy. Parts used in the 1980's were collected from both copies and are labeled 17.
  - SOMETIMES I'M HAPPY Henderson, Fletcher, 1935 (Box 25A, Folder 08)
    BG No.: S8/17/C346
    Parts: cl/saxAATTB/tpt1-4/tbn1-2/"rhythm"(4)D
    Same arrangement as BG no.C346/SB/7.
  - SOMETIMES I'M HAPPY Cohn, Al (Box 25A, Folder 09)
    BG No.: D77/19
    Parts: cl/saxT/tbn/PGBD
  - SONG IS ENDED, THE Goodman, Thomas, 1951 (Box 25A, Folder 10)
    BG No.: A292
    Tpt2 differs slightly from score. Complete.
  - SONG IS YOU, THE Powell, Mel (Box 25A, Folder 11)
    BG No.: B197
  - SONG IS YOU, THE Sauter, Eddie, 1939 (Box 25A, Folder 12)
    BG No.: C321/A78/15A
    Parts: saxT(-T1)/tpt2/PGBD
  - SONG OF INDIA Lipman, Joe, 9/1961 (Box 25A, Folder 13)
    BG No.: G31/D406
  - SONG OF THE ISLANDS Sauter, Eddie, 1941 (Box 25B, Folder 14)
    BG No.: B125/36E
  - SONG OF THE ISLANDS Hensel, Wes, c.1960 (Box 25B, Folder 15)
    BG No.: A19
    Parts: cl/saxAT/tpt/tbn/GBDV
  - SONG OF THE ISLANDS Stegmeyer, Bill, 1/1961 (Box 25B, Folder 16)
    BG No.: D340/63
  - SONG OF THE PLOW Hill, Alex, 1934 (Box 25B, Folder 17)
    BG No.: B283/70
  - SONG OF THE WANDERER Henderson, Fletcher, 1947 (Box 25B, Folder 18)
    BG No.: A138/119
    Includes full set of photocopied parts minus piano. Complete.
  - SOON Gutesha, Bobby, 1958 (Box 25B, Folder 19)
    BG No.: D53/236
  - SOON Sauter, Eddie, 1939 (Box 25B, Folder 20)
    BG No.: A89/159
    Parts: cl/saxAATTB/tpt1-4/tbn1-3/PGBD/vocal (labeled "voice/group")
  - SOON IT'S GONNA RAIN Napp, Ken (Box 25B, Folder 21)
    BG No.: G119/S9
    Parts: fl/cl1-3/bscl/tpt1-3/tbn1-3/PGBD
  - SOUND OF MUSIC, THE Karlin, Fred, 10/21/1959 (Box 25B, Folder 22)
    BG No.: D220/11
  - SOUTH Jenkins, Gordon, 4-5/1976 (Box 25C, Folder 23)
    BG No.: G151
    All sax parts double flute or clarinet. Includes alternate saxA2 part doubling clarinet instead of flute. Complete.
  - SOUTH SEA ISLAND MAGIC Stegmeyer, Bill, 1961 (Box 25C, Folder 24)
    BG No.: D332/57
  - SPANISH TOWN Henderson, Fletcher, c.1938 (Box 25C, Folder 25)
    BG No.: C262/33/B183
    Parts: cl/saxAATT/tbn1-2/PGBD
  - SPIDER AND THE FLY, THE Norman, Fred, 12/18/1938 (Box 25C, Folder 26)
  - SPIN A RECORD O'Farrill, Chico, 1949 (Box 25C, Folder 27)
  - SPINNING WHEEL Newsom, Tommy, 7/1969 (Box 25C, Folder 28)
    BG No.: G12
  - SPINNING WHEEL Foster, Frank, 1969 (Box 25C, Folder 29)
    BG No.: G101
  - SPREADIN' RHYTHM AROUND Murphy, Spud, 1935 (Box 25C, Folder 30)
    BG No.: B286/66
  - SPRING IS HERE Albam, Manny; Cohn, Al, 1959 (Box 25D, Folder 31)
    BG No.: D213
    Parts: cl/saxT/tbn/PGBD/vocal
  - SPRING RHAPSODY Burns, Ralph (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - SPRING SONG Henderson, Fletcher, 1939 (Box 25D, Folder 32)
    BG No.: 11A
    Parts: saxAATTB/tpt1-4/tbn1-3(2)/PGBD
    Includes complete set of photocopies.
  - SPRING THEME/BACH GOES TO TOWN/SWEET CLARINET Burns, Ralph (Box 34, Folder 04)
  - SPRING WILL BE LATE McFarland, Gary, 4/1962 (Box 25D, Folder 33)
    BG No.: D433/287
  - SQUEAK HEARD 'ROUND THE WORLD, THE Sauter, Eddie, 1942 (Box 25D, Folder 34)
    BG No.: C320/115A
    Parts: cl/saxAATTBBs/tpt1/tbn1-2/GBD
  - SQUEEZE ME Henderson, Fletcher, 1939 (Box 26, Folder 01)
    BG No.: 272
  - STALIN, 1946 (Box 26, Folder 02)
    BG No.: C247
    Parts: saxAATTB/tpt1-4/tbn1-2/PGBD
  - STARDUST Henderson, Fletcher (Box 26, Folder 03)
    BG No.: 8/12A/B126
  - STARDUST Jenkins, Gordon, 5/1976 (Box 26, Folder 04)
    BG No.: G145
    Parts: cl/saxA1-2/saxT1-2/saxB/tpt1-4/tbn1-4/PGBD/cond-booth
  - STARDUST Henderson, Fletcher, 1/24/1946 (Box 26, Folder 05)
    BG No.: B126
    Parts are recopies. Complete.
  - STARDUST Henderson, Fletcher, 1936 (Box 26, Folder 05A)
    BG No.: B126/8/6/S12
    1948 recopy.
  - STARS AND STRIPES Newsom, Tommy, 1962 (Box 26A, Folder 06)
    BG No.: F20
  - STAY ON THE RIGHT SIDE OF THE ROAD Henderson, Horace; Woode, Henri (Box 26A, Folder 07)
    BG No.: B102
  - STEALIN' APPLES Henderson, Fletcher (Box 26A, Folder 08)
    BG No.: 110
    Parts are recopies.
  - STEALIN' APPLES Henderson, Fletcher, 1939 (Box 26A, Folder 09)
    BG No.: B366/S13
    Parts: cl/saxAATTB(2)/tpt1-3/tbn1-3(2)/B
    Extra saxB and tbn3 parts are recopies. Bass part is photocopy.
  - STEALIN' APPLES Henderson, Fletcher, 1939 (Box 26A, Folder 10)
    BG No.: C338
    Parts: saxAATTB/tpt1-4/tbn1/GB
    All parts include an optional intro. Last chorus differs from 1939 version in sax parts. 1949 recopy.
  - STEALIN' APPLES Henderson, Fletcher, 1939 (Box 26A, Folder 11)
    BG No.: 6/B366
    1946 recopy.
  - STEALIN' APPLES Karlin, Fred, 5/29/1960 (Box 26B, Folder 12)
    BG No.: D307/43
  - STEALIN' APPLES, 1948 (Box 26B, Folder 13)
    BG No.: C213/86
    Parts: cl/saxAATT/tpt2-3/tbn1-2/PGBD
  - STEALIN' APPLES (Box 26B, Folder 14)
    BG No.: B366
    All parts (except saxB) are photocopies. This version is a transcription from the original for Glenn Gray.
  - STEALIN' APPLES Henderson, Fletcher, 1939 (Box 26A, Folder 11A)
    BG No.: 14/B366/S13
    C1 part is a photocopy. This set was used in the 1980's and is collected from various copies.
  - STEP RIGHT UP Nelson, Oliver, c.1962 (Box 26B, Folder 15)
    BG No.: D420/283
  - STEPPIN' LIGHTLY Edwards, Teddy, 8/1964 (Box 26B, Folder 16)
    BG No.: F126
  - STOLEN LOVE Grove, Dick, 6/1964 (Box 26B, Folder 17)
    BG No.: F115
  - STOLEN LOVE May, Billy, 6/10/1964 (Box 26C, Folder 18)
  - STOMPIN' AT THE SAVOY Sampson, Edgar, 1936 (Box 26C, Folder 19)
    BG No.: 28A/S14/42
    Parts: cl/saxAATTB(2)/tpt1-4/tbn1-3/PGBD
    Parts are from later expansion of original instrumentation.
    Cl/tpt1 parts labeled S14/B35
  - STOMPIN' AT THE SAVOY Burns, Ralph (Box 33, Folder 05)
  - STOOGE, THE Knepper, Jimmy, 5/1962 (Box 26C, Folder 20)
    BG No.: D418/301
  - STOP KICKING MY HEART AROUND Henderson, Fletcher, 1938 (Box 26C, Folder 21)
    BG No.: C225/124
    Parts: cl/saxAAT(-T1)/tpt1-3/tbn1-2/PGBD
  - STOP LOOK AND LISTEN Rose, David, 1936 (Box 26C, Folder 22)
    BG No.: B244
  - STOP LOOK AND LISTEN Henderson, Fletcher, 1936 (Box 26C, Folder 23)
    BG No.: B244/20
    Score covered with detailed pencil drawings.
  - STORMY WEATHER Stegmeyer, Bill, 7/1960 (Box 26C, Folder 24)
    BG No.: D328/409
  - STRANGE FRUIT Henderson, Fletcher, 1939 (Box 26D, Folder 25)
    BG No.: A20
  - STRIKE UP THE BAND Gutesha, Bobby, 1958 (Box 26D, Folder 26)
    BG No.: D54/231
  - STRING OF PEARLS Burns, Ralph (Box 34, Folder 08)
  - SUGAR Henderson, Fletcher, 1947 (Box 26D, Folder 27)
    BG No.: B28/121
  - SUGAR FOOT STOMP Todd, Tommy, 1947 (Box 26D, Folder 28)
    BG No.: B36
  - SUKIYAKA Newsom, Tommy, 6/1964 (Box 26E, Folder 29)
    BG No.: F109
  - SUMMER SOUVENIRS, 1938 (Box 26E, Folder 30)
    BG No.: 203
    On the inside of the sax and brass parts another arrangement, in F also, is penciled.
  - SUN SHINES NELLIE Sauter, Eddie, 1939 (Box 26E, Folder 31)
    BG No.: A277/231
  - SUNDAY Henderson, Fletcher, 1939 (Box 26E, Folder 32)
    BG No.: B184/324/177E
  - SUNNY DISPOSISH Murphy, Spud, 1935 (Box 26E, Folder 33)
    BG No.: 131/224
    Parts: cl/saxAATT/tpt1-2/tbn1-2/PGB
  - SUNRISE SERENADE Henderson, Fletcher, 1939 (Box 26E, Folder 33A)
    BG No.: 5/101/B16
    Photocopies only.
  - SUNSHINE OF MY LIFE, c.19 (Box 26E, Folder 34)
    BG No.: G127
  - SUPERMAN Sauter, Eddie, 1940 (Box 26E, Folder 35)
    BG No.: D4/48A
    Parts: cl/saxAATTB/tpt2-3/tbn1-2/PGBD
    Arrangement to feature Cootie Williams. Incomplete PARTS.
  - SWANEE RIVER Henderson, Fletcher, 1939 (Box 27, Folder 01)
    Score: photocopy (for original see BG no.B186/5A)
    Parts are a later recopy. Complete.
  - SWANEE RIVER Henderson, Fletcher, 1939 (Box 27, Folder 02)
    BG No.: B186/5A
    Score: original and recopy in another hand
    Parts: cl/saxAATTB/tpt1-3/tbn1-3/PG(2)BD
    Recopied score is transposed and includes saxB, added by Harrison Cooper. Complete.
  - SWANEE RIVER Henderson, Fletcher (Box 27, Folder 03)
    BG No.: B186/110/72
    Parts: saxAAT(2)TB(2)/tpt1,3/tbn1/B
    This arrangement is not the same as BG no.B186/5A. SaxA1 is unfinished. SaxA2T1B (marked BG no-72) are in Henderson's own hand.
  - SWEET AND HOT Murphy, Spud, 1935 (Box 27, Folder 04)
    BG No.: A229/123
  - SWEET AND LOVELY, c.1934 (Box 27, Folder 05)
    BG No.: A139/9
  - SWEET AND LOVELY Henderson, Fletcher, 1947 (Box 27, Folder 06)
    BG No.: A139/72
  - SWEET AND LOVELY, 1948 (Box 27A, Folder 07)
    BG No.: 104
    Clarinet part marked "Stanley"; saxT marked "Wardell"; guitar marked "Billy".
  - SWEET AND SLOW Henderson, Fletcher, 1935 (Box 27A, Folder 08)
    BG No.: 24/51/108
    Also includes extra saxT2 and saxB, parts which differ slightly.
    Parts are marked "Ray McKinley Orchestra".
  - SWEET AND SLOW Henderson, Fletcher, 1935 (Box 27A, Folder 09)
    BG No.: B212/66/4
  - SWEET AS A SONG Henderson, Fletcher, 1938 (Box 27A, Folder 10)
    BG No.: 194
  - SWEET AS A SONG Sampson, Edgar, 1937 (Box 27A, Folder 11)
    BG No.: B274/45
  - SWEET CLARINET Edwards, Teddy, 1964 (Box 27A, Folder 12)
    BG No.: F133
    Parts: cl/saxTB/tpt1-2/tbn/PBD/choir(4)
    Includes separate vocal score. Complete.
  - SWEET DREAMS SWEETHEART Woode, Henri, 1935 (Box 27A, Folder 13)
    BG No.: B273/9
  - SWEET GEORGIA BROWN Aless, Tony, 1961 (Box 27B, Folder 14)
    BG No.: B272
  - SWEET GEORGIA BROWN Powell, Mel, 1954 (Box 27B, Folder 15)
    Parts: cl/tpt/PGD
    On the reverse side of the piano part there is a sketch score of "Benny's Bugle".
  - SWEET GEORGIA BROWN, 1948 (Box 27B, Folder 16)
    BG No.: 139
  - SWEET GEORGIA BROWN Murphy, Spud, 2/23/1935 (Box 27B, Folder 17)
    Parts: no
    On "Glen Gray and Casaloma Orchestra" manuscript paper.
  - SWEET IS THE WORD FOR YOU Mundy, Jimmy, 1937 (Box 27B, Folder 18)
    BG No.: B104/96
  - SWEET LEILANI Stegmeyer, Bill, 1961 (Box 27B, Folder 19)
    BG No.: D333/58
  - SWEET LITTLE YOU Murphy, Spud, 3/6/1935 (Box 27C, Folder 20)
    BG No.: B275/80/53
  - SWEET LORRAINE Thompson, Johnny, 1943 (Box 27C, Folder 21)
    BG No.: C277/118A
    Parts: cl/saxAATTB/tpt1-3/tbn1-2/GD
  - SWEET LORRAINE Winterhalter, Hugo, 1946 (Box 27C, Folder 22)
    BG No.: A75
  - SWEET LORRAINE Henderson, Fletcher, 1941 (Box 27C, Folder 23)
    BG No.: B187
    Parts are a later recopy.
  - SWEET STRANGER Mundy, Jimmy, 1937 (Box 27C, Folder 24)
    BG No.: B276
  - SWEETHEART Powell, Mel, 1946 (Box 27C, Folder 25)
    BG No.: 26A
    Clarinet part is 3 stave condensed score (transposed). Complete.
  - SWEETHEARTS ON PARADE Lipman, Joe, 11/1961 (Box 27D, Folder 26)
    BG No.: D405/253
  - SWEETIE PIE Carter, Benny, 1934 (Box 27D, Folder 27)
    BG No.: C341/68
    Parts: saxA(2)ATT/tpt1(2)-3(2)/tbn1-2/PBD/banjo
  - SWIFT AS THE WIND Dameron, Tadd, 1962 (Box 27D, Folder 28)
    BG No.: G28/264
  - SWING HIGH, SWING LOW Mundy, Jimmy, 1937 (Box 27D, Folder 29)
    BG No.: B277
  - SWING IN B FLAT MINOR Sampson, Edgar, 1938 (Box 27D, Folder 30)
    BG No.: B106/21
  - SWING INTO SPRING Burns, Ralph (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - SWING INTO SPRING TAG Davis, Buster (Box 34, Folder 03)
  - SWING MAN Woode, Henri, 1936 (Box 27D, Folder 31)
    BG No.: B105/6
  - SWINGIN' A DREAM Henderson, Fletcher, 1939 (Box 27D, Folder 32)
    BG No.: A31
    From Broadway musical "Swingin' A Dream".
  - SWINGIN' ON A RESERVATION Mundy, Jimmy, 1937 (Box 27E, Folder 33)
    BG No.: B278
  - SWINGIN' ON A STAR Karlin, Fred, 5/19/1960 (Box 27E, Folder 34)
    BG No.: D306/39
  - SWINGIN' ON THIRDS Powell, Mel, 1946 (Box 27E, Folder 35)
    BG No.: D29
  - SWINGIN' THE RUSTY GATE Conniff, Ray, c.1945 (Box 27E, Folder 36)
    BG No.: A228
  - SWINGING DOWN THE LANE Henderson, Fletcher, 1938 (Box 27E, Folder 37)
    BG No.: B185/97
  - TAIN'T SO - HONEY, TAIN'T SO Sauter, Eddie, 1941 (Box 28, Folder 01)
    BG No.: B246
  - TAIN'T WATCHA' DO Mundy, Jimmy, 1939 (Box 28, Folder 02)
    BG No.: A377
  - TAKE A NUMBER FROM ONE TO TEN Bassman, George, 1934 (Box 28, Folder 03)
    BG No.: C116/110
  - TAKE ANOTHER GUESS Mundy, Jimmy, 1936 (Box 28, Folder 04)
    BG No.: A376/171
  - TAKE FIVE Bryant, Bobby, 5-6/1962 (Box 28, Folder 05)
    BG No.: D427/291
  - TAKE IT Gibson, Margie, 1/3/1941 (Box 28, Folder 06)
    BG No.: B213
  - TAKE MY HEART Mundy, Jimmy, 1937 (Box 28, Folder 07)
    BG No.: B13/117
  - TAKE THE "A" TRAIN Gutesha, Bobby, 1958 (Box 28, Folder 08)
    BG No.: D55/223A
  - TAKING A CHANCE ON LOVE Van Lake, Turk; Cohn, Al (Box 28, Folder 09)
    BG No.: B381
  - TAKING A CHANCE ON LOVE Norman, Fred, 3/26/1958 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    BG No.: B381/192
    Parts: cl/saxAATTB/tpt1-4/tbn1-3
  - TANGERINE Ross, Bert, 1942 (Box 28A, Folder 11)
    BG No.: B216
  - TASTE OF HONEY, A Wilson, Gerald, 12/1965 (Box 28A, Folder 12)
    BG No.: F119
    All parts (except tbn3) have an insert. An additional score for the insert is included. Complete.
  - TEA FOR TWO Cohn, Al, 1959 (Box 28A, Folder 13)
    BG No.: D79/20
  - TEARS IN MY HEART Mundy, Jimmy, 1937 (Box 28A, Folder 14)
    BG No.: B356/26/676
  - TEARS IN MY INKWELL Sauter, Eddie, 1938 (Box 28A, Folder 15)
    BG No.: A379/436
  - TENDER IS THE NIGHT Murphy, Spud, 10/1935 (Box 28A, Folder 16)
    BG No.: B241
  - THANKS A MILLION Mundy, Jimmy, 1936 (Box 28A, Folder 17)
    BG No.: C343/73
  - THANKS FOR EVERYTHING Henderson, Fletcher, c.1937 (Box 28A, Folder 18)
  - THAT LUCKY FELLOW Henderson, Fletcher, 1939 (Box 28B, Folder 19)
    BG No.: B22/123
  - THAT OLD FEELING Gutesha, Bobby, 1958 (Box 28B, Folder 20)
    BG No.: D70/259
  - THAT OLD FEELING, 1937 (Box 28B, Folder 21)
    BG No.: 212
  - THAT OLD FEELING Wootten, Red, 9/1960 (Box 28B, Folder 22)
    BG No.: D338/412
  - THAT'S A PLENTY Lipman, Joe, 1934 (Box 28B, Folder 23)
    BG No.: B30
  - THAT'S A PLENTY (Box 28B, Folder 24)
    Parts: saxATB/tpt1-3/tbn
  - THAT'S RIGHT Mundy, Jimmy, 1936 (Box 28B, Folder 25)
    BG No.: C378
    Tpt1-2 are on the same sheet of music.
  - THAT'S THE WAY IT GOES Sauter, Eddie, 1941 (Box 28B, Folder 26)
  - THAT'S WHAT YOU THINK Henderson, Fletcher, 1941 (Box 28B, Folder 27)
    BG No.: A43/33
  - THEM THERE EYES Henderson, Fletcher, 1938 (Box 28B, Folder 28)
    BG No.: C127/T7
    Score original; parts are a later recopy.
  - THEM THERE EYES (Box 28B, Folder 29)
    Parts: cl/tpt1-2/GB
  - THEM THERE EYES Henderson, Fletcher, 1939 (Box 28C, Folder 30)
    Score: photocopy (for original see BG no.C127/T7)
    Parts a later recopy. Identical to other Henderson arrangement.
  - THERE ARE SUCH THINGS Sauter, Eddie, 1943 (Box 28C, Folder 31)
    BG No.: A77
  - THERE ISN'T ANY LIMIT TO MY LOVE, c.1957 (Box 28C, Folder 32)
    BG No.: C162/210
  - THERE'LL BE SOME CHANGES MADE Henderson, Fletcher, 1938 (Box 28C, Folder 33)
    BG No.: B189
    Parts: cl(2)/saxAATTB/tpt1-3/tbn1-2/PGBD
    Parts are a later recopy. SaxB added to score in 1939. Complete.
  - THERE'S NO SUBSTITUTE FOR YOU Murphy, Spud, 4/1936 (Box 28C, Folder 34)
    BG No.: B260
  - THESE FOOLISH THINGS Mundy, Jimmy, 1936 (Box 28C, Folder 35)
    BG No.: A142/35/152E
    SaxB parts differ slightly. Complete.
  - THESE FOOLISH THINGS Mundy, Jimmy, 1936 (Box 28C, Folder 36)
    BG No.: A142/23
  - THESE FOOLISH THINGS Sauter, Eddie, 1948 (Box 28E, Folder 37)
    BG No.: A172/302
  - THEY OUGHT TO WRITE A BOOK ABOUT YOU, 1939 (Box 28E, Folder 38)
    BG No.: C22/296
  - THING OF BLUETY, A Stegmeyer, Bill, 1961 (Box 28E, Folder 39)
    BG No.: D351/68
  - THINGS I LOVE, THE Sauter, Eddie, 1941 (Box 28E, Folder 40)
    BG No.: B198
  - THIS BELIEVING WORLD Sauter, Eddie, 1941 (Box 29, Folder 01)
    BG No.: A174/125
    Feature arrangement for Billy Rodgers.
  - THIS CAN'T BE LOVE Todd, Tommy, 1947 (Box 29, Folder 02)
    BG No.: B233/121
  - THIS CAN'T BE LOVE Mundy, Jimmy, 1938 (Box 29, Folder 03)
    BG No.: C374/87/B233
    Parts: cl/saxAATT/tpt1-3/tbn2/PGBD
    Additional parts for saxA1TT labeled "6A" for a shorter arrangement in G major are included.
  - THIS COULD BE THE START Karlin, Fred, 1/13/1963 (Box 29, Folder 04)
    BG No.: F13
    Vocal arrangement. Also included are extra rhythm parts for instrumental version. Complete.
  - THIS GUY'S IN LOVE WITH YOU Knight, Peter, 1970 (Box 29, Folder 05)
    BG No.: G103/T8
    Parts: cl/saxAATTB/tpt1-2(2)3-4/tbn1-3/PGBD
    Tpt2 parts differ slightly. Complete.
  - THIS IS NEW Sauter, Eddie, 1941 (Box 29A, Folder 06)
    BG No.: B215
  - THIS IS THE MOMENT Sauter, Eddie, 1948 (Box 29A, Folder 07)
    BG No.: B361
  - THIS TIME IT'S REAL Sampson, Edgar (Box 29A, Folder 08)
    BG No.: B240
  - THOU SWELL Henderson, Fletcher, 1939 (Box 29A, Folder 09)
    BG No.: 87
  - THOUSAND DREAMS OF YOU, A Mundy, Jimmy, 1937 (Box 29A, Folder 10)
    BG No.: B1 08/197
  - THRILL IS GONE, THE Burns, Ralph, 5/1962 (Box 29A, Folder 11)
    BG No.: G30/271
  - TILL THERE WAS YOU Karlin, Fred, c.1959 (Box 29A, Folder 12)
    BG No.: 402
    Includes extra rhythm part. Complete.
  - TIME ON MY HANDS Sauter, Eddie, 1941 (Box 29A, Folder 13)
    BG No.: B214/21 A
  - TIME ON MY HANDS Cohn, Al, 1959 (Box 29A, Folder 14)
    BG No.: D80/21
  - TIME OUTDATE Durham, Eddie, 1938 (Box 29A, Folder 15)
    BG No.: B242
    Transcribed by Roy Martin.
  - TIME STANDS STILL Sauter, Eddie, 1939 (Box 29A, Folder 16)
    BG No.: B363
    Pencil drawings on score.
  - TIN ROOF BLUES Jenkins, Gordon, 5/1976 (Box 29B, Folder 17)
    BG No.: G138
    Score: full Plus 3-stave condensed score
    Photocopies only for: tPt3-4/tbn2-4/GB. Complete.
  - TINA'S CANTEEN (Box 29B, Folder 18)
    BG No.: C101/180
  - TIS AUTUMN, SO TIS Sauter, Eddie, 1941 (Box 29B, Folder 19)
    BG No.: B199
    Includes 4 page score insert labeled "girls vocal".
  - TISKET A TASKET, A Sampson, Edgar, 1938 (Box 29B, Folder 20)
    BG No.: B109
  - TO MARY WITH LOVE Mundy, Jimmy, 1937 (Box 29B, Folder 21)
    BG No.: B243
  - TOMORROW IS ANOTHER DAY Mundy, Jimmy, 1937 (Box 29B, Folder 22)
    BG No.: A259
  - TOO GOOD TO BE TRUE Mundy, Jimmy, 1937 (Box 29B, Folder 23)
    BG No.: C318/20
    Bass part marked "bass or tuba".
  - TOO MANY TEARS Stegmeyer, Bill, 6/1960 (Box 29C, Folder 24)
    BG No.: D321/49
  - TOO MARVELOUS FOR WORDS Williams, George, 1958 (Box 29C, Folder 25)
    BG No.: B389/202
  - TOO ROMANTIC Sauter, Eddie, 1940 (Box 29C, Folder 26)
    BG No.: A293
  - TOUCH OF MODERN, A Edwards, Teddy, 8/1964 (Box 29C, Folder 27)
    BG No.: F127
    Also includes part for solo trumpet (optional). Complete.
  - TRADE WINDS Sauter, Eddie, 1941 (Box 29C, Folder 28)
    BG No.: 128A/B190
  - TRANSCONTINENTAL Rose, David, 1936 (Box 29C, Folder 29)
    BG No.: A384/80
  - TREES (Box 29C, Folder 29A)
    BG No.: 60/41
  - TRIGGER FANTASY Manning, Irving, 1956 (Box 29D, Folder 30)
    BG No.: A173/179
  - TRIPLE PLAY Karlin, Fred, 1/10/1963 (Box 29D, Folder 31)
    BG No.: F11/12
  - TROUBLE IS A MAN Albam, Manny, 1948 (Box 29D, Folder 32)
    BG No.: 108
    Clarinet part marked "Stanly"; saxT marked "Wardell".
  - TRUCKIN' Henderson, Fletcher, 1936 (Box 29D, Folder 33)
    BG No.: C242/43
    Parts: saxA(-A1)TT/tpt1-3/tbn1-2/PGB
  - TRUMAN'S PORTRAIT Brant, Henry, 1945 (Box 29D, Folder 34)
    BG No.: C250
  - TUXEDO JUNCTION Henderson, Fletcher, 1939 (Box 29D, Folder 35)
    Extra clarinet part a photocopy. Parts are a recopy. Complete.
  - TWILIGHT IN TURKEY Mundy, Jimmy, 1937 (Box 29D, Folder 36)
    BG No.: A385/57
  - TWIST OF THE WRIST Sauter, Eddie, 1941 (Box 29D, Folder 37)
    BG No.: B201/17E
  - TWO HEARTS THAT PASS IN THE NIGHT Sauter, Eddie, 1941 (Box 29D, Folder 38)
    BG No.: B200
  - TWO TOGETHER Murphy, Spud, 8/19/1935 (Box 29E, Folder 39)
    BG No.: A386/46/22
    Parts: saxAT(-A2T2)/tbn3/BD
  - TWO WAY STRETCH Segure, Roger, 1943 (Box 29E, Folder 40)
    BG No.: D35/83A
    Parts: saxBs/D
  - UNCONDITIONAL SURRENDER Sauter, Eddie, 1939 (Box 29E, Folder 41)
    BG No.: B287
  - UNDECIDED Sauter, Eddie, 1938 (Box 29E, Folder 42)
    BG No.: 109
    SaxB and tbn3 from a different copy.
  - UNTIL THE REAL THING COMES ALONG Lipman, Joe, 1961 (Box 29E, Folder 43)
    BG No.: B9/U1
    Parts: cl/PG
  - UNTITLED Stegmeyer, Bill, 1961 (Box 29E, Folder 44)
    BG No.: D353/70
  - UNTITLED Williams, Mary Lou, 1948 (Box 29E, Folder 45)
    BG No.: 113
    Parts: cl2/saxT/PGB
  - UNTITLED - I Ogerman, Claus, 1961 (Box 29E, Folder 46)
    "Untitled II" on reverse side of all parts.
  - UNTITLED - II Ogerman, Claus, 1961 (Box 29E, Folder 46)
    "Untitled - I" is on reverse side of all parts. P and G are in F major; all other parts are in E flat.
  - UP A LAZY RIVER (Box 29E, Folder 47)
    BG No.: B39
  - VIE EN ROSE, LA Hyman, Dick, 6/21/1960 (Box 29E, Folder 48)
    BG No.: D317/46
  - WALTZ Knight, Peter, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 01)
    BG No.: G23/Wl
  - WANT MY MAMA Mundy, Jimmy, 1939 (Box 30, Folder 02)
    BG No.: 279
  - WARM TROPICS Henderson, Fletcher (Box 30, Folder 03)
  - WAS THAT THE HUMAN THING TO DO Todd, Tommy, 1947 (Box 30, Folder 04)
    BG No.: All
  - WAS THAT THE HUMAN THING TO DO (Box 30, Folder 05)
    BG No.: A11/218
  - WATCH IT Jenkins, Gordon, 5/1976 (Box 30, Folder 06)
    BG No.: G141
    Parts: cl(2)/saxAATTB/tpt1-4/tbn1-4/rhythm(3)D
  - WATCH WHAT HAPPENS Levinsky, Walt, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 07)
    BG No.: G14/W2
    Parts: saxAATTB/tpt1-4/tbn1-3/PGBperc
  - WAY DOWN YONDER IN NEW ORLEANS Henderson, Fletcher, 1947 (Box 30A, Folder 08)
    Score: photocopy (for original see BG no.A146/74)
    Parts are a recopy. Complete.
  - WAY DOWN YONDER IN NEW ORLEANS Henderson, Fletcher, 1947 (Box 30A, Folder 09)
    BG No.: A146/74
  - WE GO WELL TOGETHER Henderson, Fletcher, 1941 (Box 30A, Folder 10)
    BG No.: C157/69A
  - WE'LL NEVER KNOW Henderson, Fletcher, 1938 (Box 30A, Folder 11)
    BG No.: A70
  - WEEKEND IN THE COUNTRY, A Bunch, John, 1963 (Box 30A, Folder 12)
    BG No.: G122
    Parts: cl/saxT(2)/tpt/tbn/G(2)BD
    Extra guitar and saxT parts are different and may be an alternate arrangement.
  - WELL ALL RIGHT Henderson, Fletcher, 1938 (Box 30A, Folder 13)
    BG No.: A41
  - WEST OF THE WEATHER Sauter, Eddie, 1941 (Box 30B, Folder 14)
    BG No.: B289
    Parts: cl/saxAATTB/tpt1-3/tbn2/PGBD
    Clarinet part in Sauter's hand. SaxB not indicated in score.
  - WEST WIND Woode, Henri, 1936 (Box 30B, Folder 15)
    BG No.: B298/401
  - WHAT A DIFFERENCE Gutesha, Bobby, 1958 (Box 30B, Folder 16)
    BG No.: D47/229
    Parts: cl(3)/saxAATTB/tpt1-4/tbn1-4/PGBD
  - WHAT A LITTLE MOONLIGHT CAN DO Henderson, Fletcher, 1935 (Box 30B, Folder 17)
    BG No.: B67/W3/143
  - WHAT A LITTLE MOONLIGHT CAN DO Henderson, Fletcher, 1935 (Box 30B, Folder 18)